{
    "subject": "resource/Oconee_Fall_Line_Technical_College",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Education_in_Dodge_County,_Georgia",
    "human_readable": "Oconee Fall Line Technical College is about Education in Dodge County, Georgia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9501126408576965,
            "question": "Which county in Georgia houses Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.913135826587677,
            "question": "How does Oconee Fall Line Technical College contribute to the local community in Dodge County?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8804728388786316,
            "question": "Are there other educational institutions in Dodge County, Georgia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8593239784240723,
            "question": "Where is Oconee Fall Line Technical College located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8208625912666321,
            "question": "In what state is Oconee Fall Line Technical College situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7878251671791077,
            "question": "What type of institution is Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7714859843254089,
            "question": "What are some of the programs offered at Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7320598363876343,
            "question": "What does 'Technical College' suggest about Oconee Fall Line Technical College's offerings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7157182097434998,
            "question": "What is the main area of focus for Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6369987726211548,
            "question": "Are there any notable alumni from Oconee Fall Line Technical College?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Oconee Fall Line Technical College is about Education in Dodge County, Georgia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2793_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main area of focus for Oconee Fall Line Technical College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2793_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'Technical College' suggest about Oconee Fall Line Technical College's offerings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2793_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the programs offered at Oconee Fall Line Technical College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2793_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2793_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2793_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2793_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2793_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2793_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2793_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2793_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2793_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2793_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2793_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention Oconee Fall Line Technical College as a technical and vocational school serving an 11 county area in eastern Georgia, with one of those counties being Dodge County. They also describe the college's mission to contribute to the economic and workforce development of east central Georgia through quality technical and continuing education, adult education, and business and industry services. This suggests that Oconee Fall Line Technical College is indeed involved in education activities in Dodge County, Georgia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Oconee Fall Line Technical College is about education in Dodge County, Georgia.\" The documents mention that Oconee Fall Line Technical College serves eleven counties including Dodge County and offers educational programs such as associate degrees, diplomas, technical certificates of credit, and non-credit certificates."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}